https://www.hellotraveler.com/privacy-policy.html

Hello Traveler
Search:
Search
See Free Gift!
View Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Menu
Home
Categories Travel Journals  Fill-ins or Info Inside JournalsJust Lined PagesKids & Teens & Activity JournalsLeather & Almost Leather JournalsTravel OrganizersSmall-Pocket Size JournalsTravel Stickers Alphabet & Phrase StickersCaption & Journaling StickersCruise & Tropical StickersDestination StickersLuggage Labels StickersTravel-themed StickersTravel Embellishments Scrapbook Page KitsScrapbook Papers SetsTravel Gifts &Accessories Luggage TagsTravel AccessoriesTravel Photo Albums Insert Pockets 50 photos or less51 to 100 photos101 to 200 photos201 to 300 photos301 to 500 photosOther Album StylesAlbum Journal CardsTravel Picture Frames For 4 x 6 PhotosFor Other Size PhotosTravel Scrapbooks Album & Kit12 x 12 Album SizeOther Album SizesPhoto Page ProtectorsAccessoriesUnique to Us!Destinations Africa Travel GiftsAmerica Travel Gifts CentralEastGeneralHawaiiWestAsia Travel GiftsCanada Travel GiftsEurope Travel Gifts FranceItalyUnited KingdomOther CountriesInternational Travel GiftsMexico & S. America Travel GiftsThemes Beach & TropicalCruise & Transport Photo Albums & FramesScrapbooking ItemsOutdoorsRoad TripKids & Teens Journals & Activity ItemsAlbums, Scrapbooks & StickersVarious Cool ThingsWestern*DO NOT* load a cart - see Homepage for info!
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy & Security
Your personal privacy and security is very important to us. With this in mind, we offer the following information:
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you create an account on the site, place an order or utilize the Wish List feature. When ordering we will require your name, address, phone number, email address and credit card information. All of these details are fully encrypted with 256 bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We will also have information that you have provided about gift recipients so that we may ship the requested gift. The information we collect for gift recipients will not be used for marketing purposes or provided to any third party.
How do we use your information?
We use your personal data to process your order, send purchase confirmations, email shipping details and communicate with you if there is an issue related to your order. You may choose to sign up for our email Newsletter about Private Sales / New Product introductions, which we send once or twice per month. At any point you may unsubscribe from the Newsletter. Your email address will not be provided to any other entity.
Do we use "cookies"?
Cookies are small files that are placed on your computer from a web server. We use cookies to keep track of and retain the contents of your shopping cart, the Wish List feature and to customize your shopping experience. Acceptance of cookies is not required for browsing the website, however you will need to allow for them if you choose to make a purchase online. We do not use "third-party" cookies (cookies that are placed on your computer by a web server other than the site you are visiting).
How we use cookies.
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
How do we protect your information?
A variety of security measures are in place to ensure the safety of your personal data. First, we retain Business Class service from our web hosting company, Arvixe.com.
We have a security certificate from Rapid SSL which is owned and operated by GeoTrust, a leading website security provider.
When you place orders, enter or access your personal information our secure server fully encrypts that data using 256 bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. The online payment processor that we use is Authorize.net
and they do the same. A very limited number of individuals within our company have access to that information. For your safety, all credit card data is fully encrypted when you enter it and we do not have access to it.
Do we provide any of your information to third parties?
Very simply, NO. Your information is used only for the purposes of transacting business with or receiving information from Hello Traveler. The payment processor that we use (Authorize.net) must verify your name, address and credit card data in order to authorize the transaction, as is the case with any online retailer. They will have no other information related to your order and they also utilize secure servers and SSL encryption technology.
Changes to our policies.
If we need to make changes to our policies, the changes will be posted to this page.
Your consent.
By using this website, you consent to our privacy policy and indicate your awareness of our security measures.
Newsletter Sign Up
Subscribe
Once or twice per month receive an email about a Private Sale or New Product Introductions.
(anytime)
© 2005-2020 HelloTraveler.com. All Rights Reserved.
